<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CurriculumVitae</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="work">Work</string>
    <string name="edu">Education</string>
    <string name="about">About this App</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="name">Martin Kropf, BSc</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="email">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="linked_in">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="work_head">Employments</string>

    <!-- WS Routes -->
    <string name="doLogin">login</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello </string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="differentAccount">Back</string>
    <string name="noAccount"><u>No Account yet? Contact me</u></string>
    <string name="sendMail">Send email&#8230;&#8230;&#8230;</string>
    <string name="doLogin2">login2</string>
    <string name="invalidUserError">This User was not found</string>
    <string name="noConnection">The server connection timed out</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="fh_course_name">Bachelor degree programme Internet Technology</string>
    <string name="fh">FH Joanneum</string>
    <string name="year_fh">2010&#8211;2013</string>
    <string name="red_cross">Red Cross Güssing</string>
    <string name="comm_service">Community\nService</string>
    <string name="year_comm_service">2010</string>
    <string name="matriculation">A-Levels\nMain area: Informatics</string>
    <string name="borg">BORG-\nJennersdorf</string>
    <string name="year_borg">2005&#8211;2009</string>
    <string name="month_akaryon">July-November</string>
    <string name="akaryon_1">Internship/Part-Time</string>
    <string name="akaryon_2">PHP Development using CodeIgniter</string>
    <string name="year_akaryon">2012</string>
    <string name="akaryon">akaryon GmbH</string>
    <string name="year_nekom">2013&#8211;2015</string>
    <string name="nekom">Nekom GmbH</string>
    <string name="nekom_1">Android Development</string>
    <string name="nekom_2">Web Development</string>
    <string name="skill_android">After my internship as PHP-Developer I began working as an Android-Developer for the Nekom GmbH. We were mainly working on internal E-Commerce projects and showcases.</string>
    <string name="skill_android_rest">The Google Volley framework was used in addition to the GSON library for the communication between app and server. This way JSON based REST API\'s can be accessed fast and easily.</string>
    <string name="skill_android_ble">In the course of implementing a location based marketing showcase, I was able to gain experience using Bluetooth Low Energy and Beacons.</string>
    <string name="skill_android_security">Since we were working with external payment providers in our apps, security was always an important part.</string>
    <string name="skill_php">During my internship at akaryon GmbH, I was maintaining several smaller PHP projects. After my internship, I continued working part-time while continuing my studies. In this period I was part of a team which was working on a larger PHP project, using CodeIgniter and MySQL and also implemented several other frontend Projects.</string>
    <string name="skill_sketch">I have always been interested in UI and UX Design, therefore I started creating icons and other graphics myself. I decided to use Sketch for these tasks because of it\'s simplicity and ability to create whole designs and mockups in short time.</string>
    <string name="skill_git">Since we migrated from SVN to GIT in my previous company, I started using it for my private projects as well. Especially the performance and the convenient way of branching and merging influenced this decision.</string>
    <string name="androidSkills">Android</string>
    <string name="otherSkills">Others</string>
    <string name="interest_unity">Some time ago, I started developing games using the Unity-Engine. Especially the interface creation caught my attention, even though I\'m not that much of a talented designer.</string>
    <string name="interest_ios">Ever since Apple released Swift as their alternative to Objective-C for iOS development, I started trying out some tutorials for small apps.</string>
    <string name="interest_raspberry">As a central part of my bachelor thesis, I was looking into the possibilities of building and selling a working tablet, based on the Raspberry Pi. After some other small projects, the little computer is currently taking care of watering my plants on the balcony.</string>
    <string name="interests">Interests</string>
    <string name="invalidPinError">This Pin is not correct</string>
    <string name="noPinError">Please enter your pin</string>

    <string name="about_content">On the following pages the features of this app will explained in detail.</string>
    <string name="about_content2">A NodeJS Server communicating with a Mongo Database takes provides a REST API. This is used for the initial login process.</string>
    <string name="server">Server</string>
    <string name="about_content3">JSON is used as protocol for the server-app communication. The Google Volley framework takes care of all the requests and responses from and to the server\'s REST API. </string>
    <string name="communication">Communication</string>
    <string name="about_content4">All icons, graphics and screens were created using Sketch. For creating stylesheets out of these screens I used Zeplin. These stylesheets include all the measurements and color-codes which speeds up the actual development process.</string>
    <string name="about_content5">The Wikitude library was used for the Augmented-Reality area. Since I used a free license, the "Trial" watermark is displayed over the actual image.</string>
    <string name="design">Design</string>
    <string name="aboutMe">About me</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="augmented">Augmented Reality</string>
    <string name="ar_hint">Please scan the image attached in your E-Mail.</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">Please enter your Username</string>
    <string name="Logout">Logout</string>

</resources>
